<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News &#8211; Tracking Dose</title>
	<atom:link href="https://tracking.dose.com/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://tracking.dose.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 18:17:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>How long will Sunak&#8217;s &#8216;sand castle&#8217; last?</title>
		<link>https://tracking.dose.com/how-long-will-sunaks-sand-castle-last/</link>
					<comments>https://tracking.dose.com/how-long-will-sunaks-sand-castle-last/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 18:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Boris Johnson]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sage Sunak]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UK]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://tracking.dose.com/?p=29</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[UK Prime Minister Rishi Sunak has had a successful week. He can celebrate this success. Despite the good news on the economic front, those close to the UK Prime Minister say they have reminded Rishi Sunak that his castle is built on sand. The good news for the UK is that, as the International Monetary...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>UK Prime Minister Rishi Sunak has had a successful week. He can celebrate this success. Despite the good news on the economic front, those close to the UK Prime Minister say they have reminded Rishi Sunak that his castle is built on sand.</p>



<p>The good news for the UK is that, as the International Monetary Fund (IMF) said this week, the UK is not on the path to recession. Inflation and fuel prices are falling in the country. But this rate is much better than what Rishi Sunak wanted.</p>



<p>All is not well in the UK yet. But Rishi Sunak&#8217;s predecessor, Liz Truss, blundered and made economic gambles that saw the pound hit its lowest level against the dollar in a decade. Rishi Sunak can claim to have steadied the wobbly ship somewhat in the turbulent situation he took over from his predecessor.</p>



<p>But the bad news for Rishi Sunak is that his party, the Conservative Party, is still deeply divided. Various issues are still not discussed among the party members. They are fighting against each other on various issues.</p>



<p>It has not been a year since UK Prime Minister Boris Johnson was prime minister and was fighting to hold on to power in Downing Street despite scandals. During the corona epidemic, he broke the rules and threw a party. Rishi Sunak was then his Chancellor (Finance Minister). He was the one who left the cabinet after knowing the scandal of Boris Johnson and dealt a severe blow to Boris Johnson&#8217;s power.</p>



<p>Johnson&#8217;s closest allies never forgave Sunak for that betrayal. When Liz Truss stood against Sunak to take over from Boris Johnson, they all backed Liz. But Leez was forced to resign after only 49 days in power. As a result, there were no more rivals for Sunak. He became Prime Minister of the United Kingdom on October 25 last year and took an anti-lease position.</p>



<p>Rishi Sunak brought relations with Europe to a more flexible position. Johnson and Truss distanced themselves from conservatives close to them. According to the conservative right, Rishi Sunak betrayed the principle.</p>



<p>This is why Rishi has become weak in the internal politics of the Conservative Party. Two things happened this week that reminded some conservatives how quickly things can turn around.</p>



<p>The first is that Rishi has decided what to do with Home Minister Suella Braverman. Suella admitted that he sought the help of civil servants to avoid being fined for speeding in the car. Sunak ruled that Suella&#8217;s actions did not break the cabinet code. But he had to resign from the cabinet for breaking the law. Sunak quickly protected him. Because, Sunak knows he is weak to Suella. He can&#8217;t fight Zuela. Many who do not like him are with Zuela.</p>



<p>Earlier last week, Braverman spoke at an anti-Sunak conference in London. He wants to lead the Conservative Party in the future. Therefore, Suella Braverman presented her statement on that platform without paying attention to Sunak&#8217;s words.</p>



<p>The second thing is, back to Boris Johnson&#8217;s discussion. According to reports that Boris Johnson broke the rules during Corona, the matter is more serious than that. Police say Johnson broke more laws than it turned out. Boris&#8217;s allies did not take it well. They blame Sunak for this. They allege that he is behind everything. However, Rishi Sunak&#8217;s spokesperson denied the allegation.</p>



<p>Just like that two people can make Sunak&#8217;s life very difficult. They can distract from the positive headlines about the UK economy and remind everyone how quickly the Conservative Party can be divided among themselves.</p>



<p>Some of Rishi Sunak&#8217;s allies criticized Sunak for bringing Braverman to important government positions. He once had to resign from the Trus government for violating the ministerial code. Everyone knows about his ambition. Braverman is the first to step down from the ministry before the next election to take any top leadership position. If the Conservative Party loses power, that situation may also occur.</p>



<p>A senior Conservative MP told CNN that Rishi Sunak came to power knowing he was weak. He knows that he is not as strong as Boris Johnson and Liz.</p>



<p>The member added that the reality is that a very weak person like Sunak has already done a lot of damage to the party. He can step out of the shadow of Boris or Liege and form a government of his own. But his lack of confidence made them stronger in the long run.</p>



<p>A former Conservative Party adviser said if the polls did not improve, the risk of a landslide could increase. If the MPs start thinking that they cannot win the next election, some of them will decide to leave the party. The image that the party has built up for so long will crumble.</p>



<p>If a party wants to come to power, party unity is very important. Among UK political parties, the Conservative Party has historically been the most cohesive. But a senior party adviser said, &#8216;There is no hope in hell.&#8217; He commented that there is no option but to show unity like in the past before going to the next election.</p>



<p>The election consultant said, &#8216;We choose someone from the top for leadership. But if someone like Braverman is already thinking about the next leadership race, it will set a bad precedent for what&#8217;s going to happen in the next election.&#8217;</p>



<p>Rishi Sunak came to power promising a more professional approach to government. This was not seen in the previous three years in the UK. His slow and steady management style could increase votes. At the moment, no one is seriously considering trying to remove him from office.</p>



<p>Again, no one thinks that there will be an overnight change in the UK or that Boris Johnson will return to power. Many people want Rishi Sunak to remain in charge until the next election. Many people want the economy to be strengthened by his hand. But the fear is that the ugly form of the Conservative Party will begin to emerge. This will bring back factionalism and result in electoral defeat.</p>



<p>Members of the Conservative Party have been reminded of this this week. The modern Conservative Party is three steps away from collapse, an MP has said.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://tracking.dose.com/how-long-will-sunaks-sand-castle-last/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>An 8-year-old child lifts 60 kg</title>
		<link>https://tracking.dose.com/an-8-year-old-child-lifts-60-kg/</link>
					<comments>https://tracking.dose.com/an-8-year-old-child-lifts-60-kg/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 08:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[India]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[international]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[weight lifting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Weird news]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/asfdgdfhnow/?p=16</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Arshiya Goswami is eight years old. He has taken the internet by storm with his weightlifting prowess. This child from Panchkula, Haryana state of India has recently lifted 60 kg. In a video posted on social media Instagram, Arsia can be seen lifting 60 kg. He succeeded in one attempt. After lifting the weight, holding...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Arshiya Goswami is eight years old. He has taken the internet by storm with his weightlifting prowess. This child from Panchkula, Haryana state of India has recently lifted 60 kg.</p>



<p>In a video posted on social media Instagram, Arsia can be seen lifting 60 kg. He succeeded in one attempt. After lifting the weight, holding it for a while and throwing it away. After that, Arshiya is coming towards the camera in a very confident manner. Its caption read, &#8216;A very young and strong baby girl.&#8217;</p>



<p>Four days ago this video of Arsiya was released. It received more than 23 thousand responses. And the video has been viewed more than two and a half million times. Many have praised him in the comments section. One wrote, what enthusiasm, confidence. Another wrote, &#8216;One day India will be proud of you.&#8217; A third person wrote, &#8216;Much respect to you. Many adults will not be able to lift this amount of weight.&#8217;</p>



<p>Russia wants to participate in the Olympics. He is moving forward in that direction. This is why regular weight lifting. At the age of six, he won a medal in India in 2021 by lifting 45 kg. And for this extraordinary work, he got his name in the India Book of Records.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://tracking.dose.com/an-8-year-old-child-lifts-60-kg/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Erdoğan wanted F-16 fighter jets, Biden gave conditions</title>
		<link>https://tracking.dose.com/erdogan-wanted-f-16-fighter-jets-biden-gave-conditions/</link>
					<comments>https://tracking.dose.com/erdogan-wanted-f-16-fighter-jets-biden-gave-conditions/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 08:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Europe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fighter plane]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Joe Biden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NATO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Recep Tayyip Erdogan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Türkiye]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/asfdgdfhnow/?p=11</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan wants to buy advanced F-16 fighter jets from the United States. He told US President Joe Biden about this interest. But Biden gave him a counter condition. Turkey has objected to Sweden&#8217;s application to become a member of the Western military alliance NATO. Biden wants, Erdoğan will remove this objection....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan wants to buy advanced F-16 fighter jets from the United States. He told US President Joe Biden about this interest. But Biden gave him a counter condition. Turkey has objected to Sweden&#8217;s application to become a member of the Western military alliance NATO. Biden wants, Erdoğan will remove this objection.</p>



<p>Erdogan has dominated Turkish politics for two decades. First he was the Prime Minister of the country, then he became the President. He was elected as the President of Turkey for the third term last Sunday. Erdogan will lead the country with an important position in the international arena for the next five years.</p>



<p>Biden called yesterday Monday to congratulate Erdoğan after winning the election. In this phone conversation, Erdogan reiterated Ankara&#8217;s interest in buying F-16 fighter jets. Biden also informed him of Washington&#8217;s interest in NATO and the Sweden issue. Biden himself told the media about this conversation.</p>



<p>Yesterday, Biden told reporters at the White House, &#8216;I spoke with Erdogan. I congratulated Erdoğan. He (Erdoğan) still wants to do some work on F-16 fighter jets. I told him, we want an agreement with Sweden. Let&#8217;s do it together. We will get back to each other about it.&#8217;</p>



<p>Do you expect Erdoğan to take any initiative on Sweden joining NATO? Reporters ask Biden. In response, Biden said, &#8216;I raised the issue with him (Erdoğan). There will be further discussions between the US and Turkey on this next week.&#8217;</p>



<p>Sweden and Finland have been following the principle of neutrality in international politics for a long time. But after the beginning of the Russian attack on Ukraine in February last year, there was a change in the neutral policy of the two countries. Finland and Sweden think that Moscow can attack their countries as well. So the two countries want to join NATO for advance security. Because, if a member country is attacked, the rest of the NATO members will respond simultaneously. This is the rule of this military alliance.</p>



<p>Sweden and Finland applied to join NATO last year. Türkiye objected. Another NATO rule is that adding new members requires the consent of all existing members. So the initiative got stuck due to the obstruction of NATO member Turkey.</p>



<p>Later, after muddling the waters, Türkiye became flexible about Finland. Removed the objection. As a result, Finland joined NATO. But Erdogan&#8217;s Türkiye is still adamant about Sweden. Sweden&#8217;s application is also pending. So now the US, the most influential member of NATO, is trying to convince Erdogan about Sweden.</p>



<p>Meanwhile, Turkey&#8217;s interest in buying F-16 fighter jets from the US is quite old. The country is also willing to spend 2 billion dollars for this. But the US Congress objected. According to Congress, Ankara has not yet given the green signal for NATO expansion. Apart from this, questions remain about Erdoğan&#8217;s Syria policy and Turkey&#8217;s human rights situation. Therefore, the US Congress does not want to sell F-16 to Ankara for now.</p>



<p>Meanwhile, Erdoğan&#8217;s office issued a statement regarding the phone conversation with Biden. It is said that the two leaders have agreed to deepen cooperation on bilateral issues. This bilateral relationship will play an important role in meeting regional and global challenges.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://tracking.dose.com/erdogan-wanted-f-16-fighter-jets-biden-gave-conditions/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hello world!</title>
		<link>https://tracking.dose.com/hello-world/</link>
					<comments>https://tracking.dose.com/hello-world/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 08:35:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/asfdgdfhnow/?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://tracking.dose.com/hello-world/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
